<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Moscow Migrant</title>
    <link>https://moscowmigrant.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Moscow Migrant</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://moscowmigrant.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Igor Yakovenko: Putin&#39;s Koschei&#39;s Needle is Located in Crimea</title>
      <link>https://moscowmigrant.com/posts/putin-koschei-needle-is-located-in-crimea/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://moscowmigrant.com/posts/putin-koschei-needle-is-located-in-crimea/</guid>
      <description>This publication is an accurate transcription of one of the episodes from the &amp;ldquo;7-40&amp;rdquo; series on Igor Yakovenko&amp;rsquo;s channel. All information is reproduced without changes, except for corrections of errors in the automatic transcription. I would be grateful for any indications of inaccuracies or discrepancies with the original.&#xA;Good morning, dear friends! My name is Igor Yakovenko. Today is December 3rd. It is currently 7:40 in Kyiv, and one hour later in Moscow.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Am I to blame for this war?</title>
      <link>https://moscowmigrant.com/posts/am-i-to-blame-for-this-war/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://moscowmigrant.com/posts/am-i-to-blame-for-this-war/</guid>
      <description>No, I am not to blame. I see no guilt, I feel none.&#xA;I&amp;rsquo;m told that a true Russian should repent for all the crimes committed by Russia against Ukraine. But I don&amp;rsquo;t feel any guilt, and here are my arguments.&#xA;My entire being is against war, murder, and treachery. To avoid becoming a killer, I had to leave and rebuild my life from scratch. Starting over when you already have something to leave behind is difficult.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>School violence and shooting</title>
      <link>https://moscowmigrant.com/posts/school-violence-and-shooting/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://moscowmigrant.com/posts/school-violence-and-shooting/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday I read the news about a boy from Belgrade who killed 9 people in his school with his father&amp;rsquo;s gun. It was a terrible event. I feel like a monster for losing my ability to empathize with people. I lost my empathy after Russia crimes in Ukraine. In Russia we get used to negative news, so nobody would even notice. But this terrible event rises another questions in my mind.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://moscowmigrant.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://moscowmigrant.com/about/</guid>
      <description>I am from Moscow, live in Serbia, and moved here in 2022 with my small family. I can&amp;rsquo;t complain about life; we live modestly, but I have work for now.&#xA;I am constantly haunted by thoughts of why things turned out this way. Did we have a choice? Can we change something, and how? This will be the focus of my blog.&#xA;It will be available in four languages - Russian, English, Ukrainian, and Serbian.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Códigos curtos</title>
      <link>https://moscowmigrant.com/tags/shortcodes/_index.pt-br/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 11:51:36 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://moscowmigrant.com/tags/shortcodes/_index.pt-br/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
