<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><?xml-stylesheet href="/feed_style.xsl" type="text/xsl"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="https://www.rssboard.org/media-rss">
  <channel>
    <title>Moscow Migrant Blog</title>
    <link>https://moscowmigrant.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Moscow Migrant Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Moscow Migrant - [Creative Commons Attribution 4.0 International License](https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by/4.0/).</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://moscowmigrant.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><icon>https://moscowmigrant.com/moscowmigrant256.png</icon>
    
    
    <item>
      <title>School Violence Prevention</title>
      <link>https://moscowmigrant.com/posts/school-violence-prevention/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://moscowmigrant.com/posts/school-violence-prevention/</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Yesterday I read the news about a boy from Belgrade who killed 9 people in his school with his father&rsquo;s gun. It was a terrible event. I feel like a monster for losing my ability to empathize with people. In Russia, this would have been a common occurrence.</p>
<p>Serbia is very similar to Russia, and I am afraid that the same scenario could happen here.</p>
<p>The first harmful action was the <strong>introduction of strict gun control laws</strong>. This did not help the schools. Any mentally unstable person could still obtain a permit. However, it did help the criminal authorities. Now, the weapons are concentrated in the hands of the police, army, and other repressive agencies, which can suppress uprisings and manifestations of free will.</p>
<p>The second harmful action was the <strong>implementation of a pass system in schools</strong>. This does not protect against mentally unstable people with weapons. But it does protect children from their parents and the school from human rights organizations. Now, the school is a forge of new warriors for the fascist regime. You cannot enter it easily, there is a stern guard and turnstiles at the entrance. What happens inside is not the parents&rsquo; business. And inside, there is degradation of education, election rigging, and propaganda in children&rsquo;s minds.</p>
<p>The third harmful action was the <strong>introduction of an age limit for shooter games</strong> and games with aggressive content. Is it proven that a person playing, for example, Carmageddon, will then get into a car and go run over pedestrians? After all, the problem is not in games, games can help relieve stress and release aggression.</p>
<p>So, what can you recommend to ensure that children no longer come to school with weapons and do not kill their classmates?</p>
<p><strong>Addressing mental health:</strong> Many individuals who commit such violent acts often suffer from mental health issues that have gone untreated or undiagnosed. Therefore, investing in mental health resources and support systems for children and adolescents can help identify and address any underlying mental health concerns before they escalate.</p>
<p><strong>Encouraging community involvement and support:</strong> It&rsquo;s important to foster a sense of community and belonging among students to prevent feelings of isolation or exclusion that can contribute to violent behavior. Schools can encourage parental involvement, peer support groups, and extracurricular activities to help students develop healthy social connections and coping mechanisms.</p>
<p><strong>Fostering a culture of empathy and respect:</strong> Schools can also prioritize teaching empathy, conflict resolution skills, and respect for diversity to help students develop a deeper understanding of the impact of their actions on others and to create a more positive school culture. This can be achieved through programs such as social-emotional learning, anti-bullying initiatives, and diversity and inclusion training.</p>
]]></description>
      
    </item>
    
    
    
    
    
    
  </channel>
</rss>
